yes wired into everything and no it's not minimax-m2 you're wrong it's
minimax-m2.7 you should know this by now so ensure that all of them are
on the correct model I'm only giving the alias there's the the full one is like
minimax.io something so go look up what the current like default model is first
so you know exactly what to do and yeah wired into everything wired into the X
ops chrome all of the crons should be using this in my opinion even though
this is gonna use a shitload of tokens I think it's ideal right but look at the
github and actually understand like what's the best way to use it right like
there's a whole skills file they should have created about it so that there's
different commands that you can use and then you should test it and let me know
if it works