Okay now based on all of the analysis that we did here around our positioning
how to be profitable etc I have two commercialists here in Italy who are
super willing to help me and give me a hand. One of them could hire me his name
is Luigi so I want you to do a tailored message for him to either hire me or you
know like I have a price per hour okay and this project has cost me money but I
want to hire commercialisti who can get a 50% commission that no one else will
give them essentially you know what I mean I'm a builder I'm not a seller like
that's not my expertise so can you do these two tailored messages one for
Enrico who is he comes from like aerospace engineering and now he's
working on like RNA idea I don't know if you can recall or if we ever spoke about
it but it's like some RNA crisper kind of CAD style project which I pitched
agents to them but there were a bunch of like nerdy scientists that are scared
of AI so like that didn't go anywhere but Enrico who was there again background
in aerospace engineering and just became a salesman by chance he also wanted to
to help me as a matter of fact he came all the way to Perugia to speak to me
like add this in the message like how thankful I was that he came and gave me
help and that our conversation I've been sitting on it for some time and you know
I'm ready to go forward if he is on a 50% commission if he's willing to help
me solve and of course include in both these messages all of these you know
findings and you know all of our research that we've done with the
council of course don't mention the council like it's proprietary research
that we did