okay would it make sense for us to separate the front end and the back end they're already
separated services within the zooming dash youth railway project so they're already separate but
they're both pointing to the same repo and to the just to the root of the repo should we like because
i feel because what happens when i tried loading it earlier is it would just take forever and just
wouldn't load properly so i'm assuming there must be a way um for us to uh yeah like that that lag
before the site showed an internal error is what makes me think that the site is trying to load
like in the entire suit and then just crashes or something or you know like we coded way too much
we pushed we're at like two million lines of code or something by now so we need to properly
compartmentalize everything
you